[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There is no square root of two.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which movie is this conversation from:\nNate Ruffin: Coach, that... was my team. They left it in my hands. \nJack Lengyel: No... no, they did not. They just left.", "correct_answer": "We Are Marshall", "incorrect_answers": ["Rudy", "The Westing Game", "Rocky 3"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What country in Southeast Asia changed its name to Myanmar?", "correct_answer": "Burma", "incorrect_answers": ["Laos", "Cambodia", "Ethiopia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The popular breakfast cereal dish muesli was invented in 1900 in which country?", "correct_answer": "Switzerland", "incorrect_answers": ["Sweden", "Ireland", "Turkey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which continents are entirely in the Southern Hemisphere?", "correct_answer": "Australia and Antarctica", "incorrect_answers": ["South America, Africa, and Australia", "South America, Australia and Antarctica", "South America and Australia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which African American invented the traffic light?", "correct_answer": "Garrett Morgan", "incorrect_answers": ["Otis Boykin", "Lewis Latimer", "George Washington Carver"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Spanish Flu took the lives of over 40,000 people between 1918 and 1920.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Atacama Desert of Chile and Peru is one of the driest and most lifeless places on Earth. This virtually rainless plateau is made up of sand, lava flows, and what other substance?", "correct_answer": "Salt", "incorrect_answers": ["Limestone", "Clay", "Ash"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these companies recycled old sneakers to make tennis courts?", "correct_answer": "Nike", "incorrect_answers": ["Banta", "Adidas", "Reebok"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For which of these movies has Jack Nicholson not won an Oscar either for Best Actor or for Best Supporting Actor?", "correct_answer": "Chinatown", "incorrect_answers": ["One Flew Over the Cuckoos Nest", "Terms of Endearment", "As Good as It Gets"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the 39th President of the United States?", "correct_answer": "Jimmy Carter", "incorrect_answers": ["Ronald Reagan", "Bill Clinton", "Richard Nixon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the author of the childrens book Charlie and the Chocolate Factory that revolves around a boy named Charlie Bucket?", "correct_answer": "Roald Dahl", "incorrect_answers": ["A. A. Milne", "J. M. Barrie", "Lewis Carroll"]}]